https://www.robertwhite.co.uk/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Robert White
Established 1982
Professional Support Team
FREE Delivery (Conditions Apply)
International Shipping
Home
Lenses
Latest Product
LEE Filters Seven5 Sys...
LEE Filters 100mm Syst...
LEE Filters 100mm Syst...
Lens Mounts
Canon (EF)
Fuji (XF)
Hasselblad X System
Large Format (Copal)
Leica (M)
Micro Four Thirds (MFT)
Nikon (F)
Sony (E)
Latest Product
LEE Filters Seven5 Sys...
LEE Filters 100mm Syst...
LEE Filters 100mm Syst...
Colour Temperature
Infrared (IR)
Specialist Correction
Tricolour (Seperation)
Latest Product
Arca Swiss Monoball Ba...
Arca Swiss QuickLink Set
Arca Swiss C1 Cube GP ...
Latest Product
Arca Swiss Monoball Ba...
Arca Swiss QuickLink Set
Arca Swiss C1 Cube GP ...
Latest Product
Voigtlander 10.5mm f0....
Voigtlander 10mm f5.6 ...
Voigtlander 10mm f5.6 ...
Latest Product
Arca Swiss Monoball Ba...
Arca Swiss QuickLink Set
Arca Swiss C1 Cube GP ...
Sale Items
Ex-Demo Zeiss 85mm f1....
Ex-Demo Zeiss Batis 25...
Ex-Demo Zeiss 18mm f2....
Ex-Demo Zeiss 15mm f2....
Ex-Demo Zeiss 135mm f2...
Ex-Demo Zeiss 15mm f2....
Gitzo GH3382QD Series ...
Latest Product
LEE Filters Seven5 Sys...
LEE Filters 100mm Syst...
LEE Filters 100mm Syst...
Lens Mounts
Canon (EF)
Fuji (XF)
Hasselblad X System
Large Format (Copal)
Leica (M)
Micro Four Thirds (MFT)
Nikon (F)
Sony (E)
Latest Product
LEE Filters Seven5 Sys...
LEE Filters 100mm Syst...
LEE Filters 100mm Syst...
Colour Temperature
Infrared (IR)
Specialist Correction
Tricolour (Seperation)
Latest Product
Arca Swiss Monoball Ba...
Arca Swiss QuickLink Set
Arca Swiss C1 Cube GP ...
Latest Product
Arca Swiss Monoball Ba...
Arca Swiss QuickLink Set
Arca Swiss C1 Cube GP ...
Latest Product
Voigtlander 10.5mm f0....
Voigtlander 10mm f5.6 ...
Voigtlander 10mm f5.6 ...
Latest Product
Arca Swiss Monoball Ba...
Arca Swiss QuickLink Set
Arca Swiss C1 Cube GP ...
Sale Items
Ex-Demo Zeiss 85mm f1....
Ex-Demo Zeiss Batis 25...
Ex-Demo Zeiss 18mm f2....
Ex-Demo Zeiss 15mm f2....
Ex-Demo Zeiss 135mm f2...
Ex-Demo Zeiss 15mm f2....
Gitzo GH3382QD Series ...
Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Home
»
Privacy Policy
Return to Previous Page
Privacy Policy
Flaghead Photographic Ltd T/A Robert White, understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your personal data is used. We respect and value the privacy of everyone who visits this website, www.robertwhite.co.uk (“Our Site”) and will only collect and use personal data in ways that are described here, and in a way that is consistent with our obligations and your rights under the law.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and ensure that you understand it. Your acceptance of this Privacy Policy is deemed to occur upon your first use of Our Site. If you do not accept and agree with this Privacy Policy, you must stop using Our Site immediately.
1. Definitions and Interpretation
In this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings:
“Account”
means an account required to access and/or use certain areas and features of Our Site
“Cookie”
means a small text file placed on your computer or device by Our Site when you visit certain parts of Our Site and/or when you use certain features of Our Site. Details of the Cookies used by Our Site are set out in Part 14, below
“Cookie Law”
means the relevant parts of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003
2. Information About Us
Our Site is owned and operated by Flaghead Photographic Ltd., a limited company registered in England and Wales under company number 5338134.
Registered address: 4 The Axium Centre, Dorchester Road, Lytchett Minster, Poole, BH16 6FE
Main trading address: Unit 6 Alder Hills Industrial Estate, 16 Alder Hills, Poole, Dorset, BH12 4AR
VAT number: GB 854 2303 43
Email address: info@flaghead.co.uk
Telephone number: 01202 733123
Postal Address: Unit 6 Alder Hills Industrial Estate, 16 Alder Hills, Poole, Dorset, BH12 4AR
3. What Does This Policy Cover?
This Privacy Policy applies only to your use of Our Site. Our Site may contain links to other websites. Please note that we have no control over how your data is collected, stored, or used by other websites and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them.
4. What is Personal Data?
Personal data is defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (EU Regulation 2016/679) (the “GDPR”) as ‘any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified in particular by reference to an identifier’.
Personal data is, in simpler terms, any information about you that enables you to be identified. Personal data covers obvious information such as your name and contact details, but it also covers less obvious information such as identification numbers, electronic location data, and other online identifiers.
5. What Are My Rights?
Under the GDPR, you have the following rights, which we will always work to uphold:
The right to be informed about our collection and use of your personal data. This Privacy Policy should tell you everything you need to know, but you can always contact us to find out more or to ask any questions using the details in Part 15.
The right to access the personal data we hold about you. Part 13 will tell you how to do this.
The right to have your personal data rectified if any of your personal data held by us is inaccurate or incomplete. Please contact us using the details in Part 15 to find out more.
The right to be forgotten, i.e. the right to ask us to delete or otherwise dispose of any of your personal data that we have. Please contact us using the details in Part 15 to find out more.
The right to restrict (i.e. prevent) the processing of your personal data.
The right to object to us using your personal data for a particular purpose or purposes.
The right to data portability. This means that, if you have provided personal data to us directly, we are using it with your consent or for the performance of a contract, and that data is processed using automated means, you can ask us for a copy of that personal data to re-use with another service or business in many cases.
Rights relating to automated decision-making and profiling. We do not use your personal data in this way.
For more information about our use of your personal data or exercising your rights as outlined above, please contact us using the details provided in Part 15.
Further information about your rights can also be obtained from the Information Commissioner’s Office or your local Citizens Advice Bureau.
If you have any cause for complaint about our use of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.
6. What Data Do We Collect?
Depending upon your use of Our Site, we may collect some or all of the following personal and non-personal data (please also see Part 14 on our use of Cookies and similar technologies.
Name
Date of birth
Address
Email address
Telephone number
Business name
Payment information
IP address
Web browser type and version
Operating system
A list of URLs starting with a referring site, your activity on Our Site, and the site you exit to.
Tax/VAT Number.
7. How Do You Use My Personal Data?
Under the GDPR, we must always have a lawful basis for using personal data. This may be because the data is necessary for our performance of a contract with you, because you have consented to our use of your personal data, or because it is in our legitimate business interests to use it. Your personal data may be used for the following purposes:
Providing and managing your Account
Providing and managing your access to Our Site
Personalising and tailoring your experience on Our Site
Supplying our products and services to you. Your personal details are required in order for us to enter into a contract with you.
Personalising and tailoring our products and services for you.
Communicating with you. This may include responding to emails or calls from you.
Supplying you with information by email and post that you have opted-in to (you may unsubscribe or opt-out at any time by using the “Update Preferences” link in any of our newsletters.
Analysing your use of Our Site and gathering feedback to enable us to continually improve Our Site and your user experience.
With your permission and/or where permitted by law, we may also use your personal data for marketing purposes, which may include contacting you by email and post with information, news, and offers on our products and services. You will not be sent any unlawful marketing or spam. We will always work to fully protect your rights and comply with our obligations under the GDPR and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, and you will always have the opportunity to opt-out.
8. How Long Will You Keep My Personal Data?
We will not keep your personal data for any longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected. Your personal data will therefore be kept for the following periods (or, where there is no fixed period, the following factors will be used to determine how long it is kept):
Personal data supplied to us for the purpose of purchasing products or services needs be retained within our financial systems for a period of 7 years in accordance with HMRC guidelines for retaining financial information.
Personal data supplied to us when signing up to our mailing list shall be retained for that purpose only until you instruct us otherwise or unsubscribe via the link in a newsletter..
9. How and Where Do You Store or Transfer My Personal Data?
We will only store or transfer your personal data within the European Economic Area (the “EEA”). The EEA consists of all EU member states, plus Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein. This means that your personal data will be fully protected under the GDPR or to equivalent standards by law.
The security of your personal data is essential to us and to protect your data, we take a number of important measures, including the following:
We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know such data. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.
We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so. We will report any breaches or potential breaches to the appropriate authorities and to anyone affected by a breach within 72 hours.
10. Do You Share My Personal Data?
We may sometimes contract with the following third parties to supply certain services. These may include payment processing, delivery, and marketing. In some cases, those third parties may require access to some or all of your personal data that we hold.
Sonassi based in England for the purposes of Our Site user accounts and order processing.
Brightpearl based in England for the purposes of order processing.
PayPal (Europe) based in Luxembourg for the purposes of payment processing.
Braintree based in England for the purposes of payment processing.
UPS Europe based in England for the purposes of order delivery.
DPDgroup UK Ltd based in England for the purposes of order delivery.
Royal Mail Group Ltd based in England for the purposes of order delivery.
If any of your personal data is required by a third party, as described above, we will take steps to ensure that your personal data is handled safely, securely, and in accordance with your rights, our obligations, and the third party’s obligations under the law, as described above in Part 9.
If any personal data is transferred outside of the EEA, we will take suitable steps in order to ensure that your personal data is treated just as safely and securely as it would be within the UK and under the GDPR, as explained above in Part 9.
In some limited circumstances, we may be legally required to share certain personal data, which might include yours, if we are involved in legal proceedings or complying with legal obligations, a court order, or the instructions of a government authority.
11. How Can I Control My Personal Data?
In addition to your rights under the GDPR, set out in Part 5, when you submit personal data via Our Site, you may be given options to restrict our use of your personal data. In particular, we aim to give you strong controls on our use of your data for direct marketing purposes (including the ability to opt-out of receiving emails from us which you may do by unsubscribing using the links provided in our emails and at the point of providing your details and by managing your Account
You may also wish to sign up to one or more of the preference services operating in the UK: The Telephone Preference Service (“the TPS”), the Corporate Telephone Preference Service (“the CTPS”), and the Mailing Preference Service (“the MPS”). These may help to prevent you receiving unsolicited marketing. Please note, however, that these services will not prevent you from receiving marketing communications that you have consented to receiving.
12. Can I Withhold Information?
You may access Our Site without providing any personal data at all. However, to use all features and functions available on Our Site you may be required to submit or allow for the collection of certain data.
You may restrict our use of Cookies. For more information, see Part 14.
13. How Can I Access My Personal Data?
If you want to know what personal data we have about you, you can ask us for details of that personal data and for a copy of it (where any such personal data is held). This is known as a “subject access request”.
All subject access requests should be made in writing and sent to the email or postal addresses shown in Part 15. To make this as easy as possible for you, a Subject Access Request Form is available for you to use. You do not have to use this form, but it is the easiest way to tell us everything we need to know to respond to your request as quickly as possible.
There is not normally any charge for a subject access request. If your request is ‘manifestly unfounded or excessive’ (for example, if you make repetitive requests) a fee may be charged to cover our administrative costs in responding.
We will respond to your subject access request within 30 days of receiving it. Normally, we aim to provide a complete response, including a copy of your personal data within that time. In some cases, however, particularly if your request is more complex, more time may be required up to a maximum of three months from the date we receive your request. You will be kept fully informed of our progress.
14. How Do You Use Cookies?
Our Site may place and access certain first-party Cookies on your computer or device. First-party Cookies are those placed directly by us and are used only by us. We use Cookies to facilitate and improve your experience of Our Site and to provide and improve our products and services. We have carefully chosen these Cookies and have taken steps to ensure that your privacy and personal data is protected and respected at all times.
All Cookies used by us and on Our Site are used in accordance with current Cookie Law.
Before Cookies are placed on your computer or device, you will be shown a pop-up requesting your consent to set those Cookies. By giving your consent to the placing of Cookies you are enabling us to provide the best possible experience and service to you. You may, if you wish, deny consent to the placing of Cookies; however certain features of Our Site may not function fully or as intended.
Certain features of Our Site depend on Cookies to function. You may still block these Cookies by changing your internet browser’s settings as detailed below, but please be aware that Our Site may not work properly if you do so. We have taken great care to ensure that your privacy is not at risk by allowing them.
The following first-party Cookies may be placed on your computer or device:
Name of Cookie
Purpose
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Our Site uses analytics services provided by Google. Website analytics refers to a set of tools used to collect and analyse anonymous usage information, enabling us to better understand how Our Site is used. This, in turn, enables us to improve Our Site and the products and services offered through it.
The analytics service used by Our Site use Cookies to gather the required information. You do not have to allow us to use these Cookies, however whilst our use of them does not pose any risk to your privacy or your safe use of Our Site, it does enable us to continually improve Our Site, making it a better and more useful experience for you.
The analytics service used by Our Site uses the following Cookies:
Name of Cookie
First / Third Party
Provider
Purpose
_ga
first
Google
Used to distinguish users.
_gid
first
Google
Used to distinguish users.
_gat
first
Google
Used to throttle request rate. If Google Analytics is deployed via Google Tag Manager, this cookie will be named _dc_gtm_<property-id>.
AMP_TOKEN
first
Google
Contains a token that can be used to retrieve a Client ID from AMP Client ID service. Other possible values indicate opt-out, inflight request or an error retrieving a Client ID from AMP Client ID service.
_gac_<property-id>
first
Google
Contains campaign related information for the user. If you have linked your Google Analytics and AdWords accounts, AdWords website conversion tags will read this cookie unless you opt-out.
__utma
first
Google
Used to distinguish users and sessions. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utma cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
__utmt
first
Google
Used to throttle request rate.
__utmb
first
Google
Used to determine new sessions/visits. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and no existing __utmb cookies exists. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
__utmc
first
Google
Not used in ga.js. Set for interoperability with urchin.js. Historically, this cookie operated in conjunction with the __utmb cookie to determine whether the user was in a new session/visit.
__utmz
first
Google
Stores the traffic source or campaign that explains how the user reached your site. The cookie is created when the javascript library executes and is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
__utmv
first
Google
Used to store visitor-level custom variable data. This cookie is created when a developer uses the _setCustomVar method with a visitor level custom variable. This cookie was also used for the deprecated _setVar method. The cookie is updated every time data is sent to Google Analytics.
In addition to the controls that we provide, you can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser. Most internet browsers also enable you to choose whether you wish to disable all Cookies or only third-party Cookies. By default, most internet browsers accept Cookies, but this can be changed. For further details, please consult the help menu in your internet browser or the documentation that came with your device.
You can choose to delete Cookies on your computer or device at any time, however you may lose any information that enables you to access Our Site more quickly and efficiently including, but not limited to, login and personalisation settings.
It is recommended that you keep your internet browser and operating system up-to-date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser and manufacturer of your computer or device if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings.
15. How Do I Contact You?
To contact us about anything to do with your personal data and data protection, including to make a subject access request, please use the following details:
(for the attention of Eberhard Haase)
Email address: info@flaghead.co.uk
Telephone number: 01202 733123
Postal Address: Unit 6 Alder Hills Industrial Estate, 16 Alder Hills, Poole, Dorset, BH12 4AR
16. Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. This may be necessary, for example, if the law changes, or if we change our business in a way that affects personal data protection.
Any changes will be immediately posted on Our Site and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the Privacy Policy on your first use of Our Site following the alterations. We recommend that you check this page regularly to keep up-to-date.
Sign up for discounts, latest releases and news
Submit
Follow Us Facebook Twitter Youtube Email
Pay with
Ordering
Terms & Conditions
Orders & Returns
Payment Options
© 2020 Flaghead Photographic Ltd Trading as Robert WhiteMagento WebsiteDesign by Orbital.
© 2020 © 2014 Flaghead Photographic Ltd t/a Robert White Photographic
EV SSL
